chuckecheese.com 2019-10-19

# Terms & Privacy

## PRIVACY

Effective Date: August 25, 2017

CEC Entertainment Concepts, L.P. its parent company and its affiliates (collectively referred to herein as “CEC Entertainment”) are very respectful of the privacy concerns of the visitors to its site on the Internet. This privacy policy applies to www.chuckecheese.com. This privacy policy describes how CEC Entertainment collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website www.chuckecheese.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY

CEC Entertainment makes a special effort to encourage children to consult with their parents before furnishing data. However, CEC Entertainment believes that parents should supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission.

We do not seek to acquire information specifically from children under the age of 13 on the Chuck E. Cheese website or its mobile applications.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at:

CEC Entertainment  
Attn.: Marketing Department  
1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063  
Phone number: 972-258-8507  
Email address: guestrelations@cecentertainment.com

If you have an unresolved privacy or data concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Information Collection and Use

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address

We also collect the following information from you:

  * Birthdate, ages of children, shipping information, or other information that visitors voluntarily provide
  * Demographic information such as zip code to help provide you with services

We use this information to:

  * Complete party or event reservations
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send Third Party’s email confirmation about party’s 
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communication
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our website and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

#### Geo-Location Data

We do not ask you for, access or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our Mobile Applications or Services. However, our website does ask you for, access or track any location based information so that we may enhance your experience on our website (e.g., locating a nearby Chuck E. Cheese or identifying special offers that may be of interest to you, or personalizing your interactions with us). For most mobile devices, you are able to withdraw your permission for us to acquire this information on your location through the device settings. If you have questions about how to disable your mobile device's location services, we recommend you contact your mobile device service provider or the device manufacturer. If you would like us to delete location information we have collected, please contact us at the email or postal address listed below. Please note that the website may not function properly following deletion, and that we may be required by law to retain certain information. 

#### Device Information

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use and the operating system version so that we may provide you with the correct version of our application(s).

#### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

#### Service Providers

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order, processing your payment, or offering customer services. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

#### Legal Disclaimer

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * In certain situations, CEC Entertainment may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * If CEC Entertainment is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Name of third-party partner

What info is shared with or collected by this partner?

Partner’s purpose

Link to partner’s privacy policy

Google Inc. (YouTube)

Analytics, visitor traffic stats

YouTube, website tools, ad platform, analytics

<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

Microsoft (Atlas Solutions)

User Internet usage/behavior (no PII)

Ad network, advertising

<http://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/default.mspx>

Twitter Inc.

Page links

Social sharing

<https://twitter.com/privacy>

Instagram

Page links, likes

Social sharing

<https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388>

Pinterest

Page links, pins

Social sharing

<https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy>

Facebook

Page links, likes

Social sharing

<https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>

Appnexus

User Internet usage/behavior (no PII)

Ad network

<http://www.appnexus.com/en/company/privacy-policy>

Mediaplex / Conversant

User Internet usage/behavior (no PII)

Ad platform

<http://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy>

Double Click

User Internet usage/behavior (no PII)

Ad platform

<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

Google Adsense

User Internet usage/behavior (no PII)

Ad network

<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

The chart lists the names of some of our third party partners and support provider entities, which may provide administrative services to our Websites. These entities may change from time to time and we will update this list as soon as practicable following any changes.

If you have any inquiries regarding our partner’s privacy practices or how they use your child’s personal information, please contact us directly at [guestrelations@cecentertainment.com](mailto:guestrelations@cecentertainment.com). 

User Access and Choice Upon your request CEC Entertainment will confirm for you whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update, or request deletion of personally identifiable information collected by contacting us by emailing our Customer Support at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. To safeguard your information, we will also take steps to verify your identity before granting access or correction. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. Although we do not seek to collect information from children, parents may, after providing proper parental identification, request to review, update, or delete their own child's information that may have been submitted and refuse to allow CEC Entertainment to collect further information about their child by emailing our Customer Support at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. Parents who provide information of their under 13 child can consent to collection and use of their child's personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Opt-out Preferences

Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails. We do send transactional emails when processing your orders and responding to your feedback/questions. You may not opt out of these emails as they are not promotional in nature.

#### Reservation Deposits

We require a non-refundable $50 deposit to secure your reservation.  The deposit will be applied towards your party total on the day of the party.  Your reservation may be cancelled and/or rescheduled at any time.  If you need to cancel, your reservation the non-refundable deposit can be used towards a new reservation within one (1) year of the reserved date of the party that was cancelled.  The billing descriptor you will see on your credit/bank statement will be portrayed as “CHUCK E CHEESE DEPOSIT”

#### Agreement to Contact Us

 ****We are eager to offer the best customer experience possible. Please contact our Guest Relations team prior to contacting your credit card issuer to allow us to resolve any issues or concerns with our services.  You can reach us by email at ceconline@cecentertainment.com   or toll-free at 833-268-2201.  We are available from (Monday-Friday 8am-5pm (CT)). Expect a 72-hour response time for email inquiries.

#### Surveys

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as ZIP code).We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter, or contact if there are issues. We may use a third-party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

#### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts are used by us and our tracking utility company who provides online customer support. These technologies are used in improving the user experience for completing forms for the reservation process, tracking behaviors so that we can provide relevant messaging and improve the overall experience, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

#### Analytics / Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This data is used to track Internet usage and behavior so that we can retarget you with relevant messaging and to improve the user experience.

#### Local Storage (HTML5)

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity use Local Storage also known as HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

#### Behavioral Advertising/Retargeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

#### Data Supplementation

We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. Examples of the types of personal information that may be obtained from public sources or purchased from third parties and combined with information we already have about you, may include:

  * Address information about you from third party sources, such as the U.S. Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.
  * Purchased marketing data about our customers from third parties that is combined with information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products.

#### Mobile Analytics

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile application, as we do not collect any personal information through the application.

#### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com.

#### Additional Information Links to Third-Party Sites

Our site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of CEC Entertainment. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.To provide certain animated features on our site, we use Macromedia Shockwave, Macromedia Flash, Adobe Acrobat, and Apple's QuickTime ActiveX plugins, which will automatically prompt you for download if your browser does not contain the latest version. Apple and Adobe use the information collected through these applications according to their own privacy and security policies, which can be further evaluated at: <http://www.apple.com/quicktime> and [http://www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/)

#### Testimonials

#### 

From time to time, we display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [guestrelations@cecentertainment.com](mailto:guestrelations@cecentertainment.com).

#### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button and widgets, such as the “Share this” button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 allows our California customers to request certain information regarding our disclosures in the prior calendar year, if any, of personally identifiable information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at either [guestrelations@cecentertainment.com](mailto:guestrelations@cecentertainment.com) or CEC Entertainment,1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063, Attn: Marketing Department, and include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond. We will attempt to provide you with the requested information within thirty (30) days of receipt.

#### Changes To This Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices at any time. Notice will be given when the privacy policy is changed. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

#### Contact Us

CEC Entertainment  
Attn.: Marketing Department  
1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063  
Phone number: 972-258-8507  
Email address: [guestrelations@cecentertainment.com](mailto:guestrelations@cecentertainment.com)

#### TERMS OF USE

Please read these Terms Of Use carefully before using this site. By using this site, you are agreeing to these Terms Of Use. If you do not agree with any of the below Terms Of Use, do not use this site. CEC Entertainment Concepts, L.P. (CEC Entertainment) reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms Of Use at any time and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.

Regardless of changes in these Terms Of Use, personally identifiable information will never be used in ways materially different than stated in these Terms of Use without first providing you a meaningful opportunity to opt out or prevent that use.

#### TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS AND RESTRICTIONS

This site is controlled and operated by CEC Entertainment, 1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063. The phone number is 972-258-8507. Email address guestrelations@cecentertainment.com. All materials on this site, including, but not limited to images, illustrations, audio clips, and video clips, are protected by copyrights that are owned and controlled by CEC Entertainment or by other parties that have licensed their material to CEC Entertainment. (“Copyrights”). Material from [www.chuckecheese.com](http://www.chuckecheese.com/) or any website owned, operated, licensed or controlled by CEC Entertainment (“CEC Entertainment websites”) may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of the copyrights and other proprietary rights. For purposes of this Terms of Use Agreement, the use of any such material on any other website or networked computer environment is prohibited.

#### WARRANTIES DISCLAIMER

Materials on the Chuck E. Cheese website are provided “as is” and without warranties of any kind either express or implied. To the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, CEC Entertainment disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. CEC Entertainment does not warrant that the functions contained in the materials will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, nor the server that makes them available are free of viruses or other harmful components. CEC Entertainment does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials in CEC Entertainment websites in terms of their correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. You (and not CEC Entertainment) assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair or correction. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you. Material on the Chuck E. Cheese website is provided solely for entertainment and promotional purposes. Any notes, message/billboard postings, ideas, suggestions, concepts or other material submitted will become the property of CEC Entertainment throughout the universe and CEC Entertainment, subject only to the privacy portions of this statement controlling the use of personally identifiable information, shall be entitled to use the material for any type of use forever including in any media whether now known or hereafter devised. You agree to indemnify CEC Entertainment and its officers, directors, employees, agents, distributors and affiliates from and against any and all third-party claims, demands, liabilities, costs, or expenses, including reasonable attorney’s fees, resulting from your breach of any of the foregoing agreements, representations, and warranties.

#### EMAILS AND POSTINGS RECEIVED

Do not post any threatening or libelous emails or material on this site that would be considered a violation of any law. CEC Entertainment will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing CEC Entertainment to disclose the identity of anyone posting any such emails or materials.

#### JURISDICTIONAL ISSUES

Unless otherwise specified, the materials in Chuck E. Cheese website are presented solely for the purpose of entertainment and promotion. This site is controlled and operated by CEC Entertainment from its offices within the State of Texas, United States of America. CEC Entertainment makes no representation that materials in Chuck E. Cheese website are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. This agreement shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Texas, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such State. Any action you, any third party or CEC Entertainment bring to enforce this agreement or, in connection with, any matters related to this site shall be brought only in either the state or Federal Courts located in Dallas, Texas and you expressly consent to the jurisdiction of said courts. If any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by CEC Entertainment. Except for disputes regarding the collection and use of personally identifiable information, which may be processed through the TRUSTe Privacy Dispute Resolution Service, this agreement shall otherwise be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Texas, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such State. Any action you, any third party or CEC Entertainment bring to enforce this agreement or, in connection with, any matters related to this site shall be brought only in either the state or Federal Courts located in Dallas, Texas and you expressly consent to the jurisdiction of said courts. If any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by CEC Entertainment.

#### JOB APPLICANT SMS

When you provide your telephone number as part of your application for employment with CEC Entertainment you agree to receive text/SMS messages concerning future job opportunities subject to the terms below.  

IMPORTANT NOTE: By opting in to receive text/SMS messages you are also opting in to receive autodialed ads and other marketing messages/calls. By opting in you agree that CEC Entertainment may send you up to six (6) text/SMS  autodialed ads and other marketing messages. Residents of Canada are not eligible to receive Text/SMS messages and will not be provided the ability to opt-in.

By providing us your mobile telephone number and opting-in to such calls and text/SMS messages, you represent that you are the owner of the mobile telephone associated with that mobile telephone number and that you are responsible for controlling access to that mobile telephone. You agree to notify CEC Entertainment of any change to your mobile telephone number. If you opt-in to receive autodialed and prerecorded calls or text/SMS messages from CEC Entertainment and then change your mobile telephone number, you agree that CEC Entertainment may continue to send text/SMS messages, or autodialed and prerecorded calls to you at the new mobile telephone number unless you opt-out as described below. Depending on the terms of your service agreement with your mobile telecommunications service provider message and data rates may apply to the text/SMS messages and autodialed and prerecorded call that CEC Entertainment send to your mobile telephone number. Supported carriers for CEC Entertainment text/SMS messages are: AT&T, Verizon, T-Mobile, and Metro PCS (at a minimum.) Please note, T-Mobile is not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.

Your consent is not a condition of making any employment decisions. Message and data rates may apply. For help, text HELP to 972-449-7899.  
HOW TO OPT-OUT OF AND STOP TEXT/SMS MESSAGES:

If you wish to opt-out of and stop receiving text/SMS messages from CEC Entertainment, reply to our text/SMS message with “STOP” or by sending “STOP” to  972-449-7899.

If you opt-in to receive text/SMS messages from CEC Entertainment and later opt-out of receiving text/SMS messages from us, you agree that CEC Entertainment may send a text/SMS message to your mobile telephone number to confirm that you have opted-out of receiving text/SMS messages from us.
